bitshare.com 2012-10-03

# BitShare.com - Free File Hosting and Cloud Storage

BitShare takes your personal privacy seriously. We will not disclose any personal information about you without your prior approval.  
In general, any information you provide to our team while contacting us will only be used within BitShare.

  * **IP addresses of users**  

Our servers can detect the IP address of your browser according to Internet-technology. This IP address is registered by BitShare.com servers especially for our internal use (registration of use, optimal downloads use and so on).

  * **E-mail**  

Our server writes in the register of BitShare.com users emails only for their registration and calculation. Under no circumstances will BitShare.com lease, sell, or provide your personal information to any companies.

  * **Cookies use.**  

BitShare.com uses cookies for the users’ comfort in order to save the browser settings. BitShare.com does not any methods for tracking users (the so-called “spy” or “1x1” gif images and so on).

  * **Safe operation with files.**  

We have taken the appropriate security measures at the servers’ physical location to protect from loss, incorrect usage, or change of information provided to us by the users of the service. Files, saved for delivery can be accessible only to BitShare.com representatives or via a link provided to the recipient. All files saved by our service are deleted after a certain time period if you do not delete them yourself.

  * **Credit card information.**  

All purchases on BitShare.com are handled by a third paryt pay system - Paypal.com. in which the transferred information thereof is encrypted. BitShare.com does not arrange and save numbers or any information from your credit card.

  * **Advertisements.**

Advertisements located on our website can be posted by third party advertisement company. These companies can use the information regarding your visits on these or other web pages (your name, address, e-mail, and phone number are excluded) to place an advertisement of products and services that might be interesting to you.  

  * **NOTE.**

We can disclose your personal information in case it becomes necessary to defend our juridical rights.  
Especially if your information is connected with tangible or assumed saboteur actions or poses a potential threat to any personal's physical safety.  
Disclosure of your information can be lawful or as a result of a legal process.  

We reserve the right to add, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy at any time.  
If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please conctact us **here**
